[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Is it relevant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "There's no significance that there was trace amounts of marijuana in Trayvon Martin's system.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "So should we be taking this at literally face value?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, again, you have to put it in context, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "And on behalf of the family, are you basically accepting now from everything you've seen and from the stuff that's come out today, there clearly was a physical fight between them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Well, Piers, the family has always said that if there was an altercation that it was started by George Zimmerman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "How significant is that in relation to any defense that George Zimmerman might have on the stand your ground?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "The crux of the matter, Piers, is if George Zimmerman stays in that car, if he does what every neighborhood watchman tells and instructs and teaches him to do, none of this happens.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "I know you can't talk for legal reasons about any of the specifics of the new evidence, but on a general level, what is your reaction to all this coming out now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "DT", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Well, we knew it was coming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Do you accept as one unequivocal, undeniable fact that if George Zimmerman had stayed in his car then none of this would have happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Yes, as simply as if Trayvon Martin hadn't been in the complex, none of this could have happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Is that really where we are with this case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "I think that a lot of people believe that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Am I right in thinking there are still a chance, perhaps even quite a good chance, that this may never come to a full trial?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, the only way that would happen of course is if some resolution beforehand, and that could include any type of pretrial motions that might end in the dismissal of the charges.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "What is your overview of its significance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Well, there's a lot to digest in a very short period of time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Was it a shock to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "No, they never did and I never heard that in all of this time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "What was she like, Donna Summer, from your experience?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "I thought she was a very gracious and a very nice person.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donna Summer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "I mean how does she rank do you think as a singer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "A very good singer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Did you have a favorite song by Donna?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "RANKLIN: I liked a lot of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donna"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "What do you think from a singing point of view she would have liked her legacy to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "I think probably just exactly what it was, she was a reigning queen of disco.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "It's a sad day, isn't it, Aretha?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "It is really a sad day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "So how long would the risk of exposure exist to somebody from this kind of inhalation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Yes, it's a really good question, Piers, and there's sort of a couple of things at play here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "I guess, Sanjay, we'll never really know, will we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I think we're unlikely to know certainly in her case.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sanjay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "That is really offensive, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "It's more than offensive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "IN", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Are you as disgusted by this as Mitt Romney seems to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I haven't seen a particular ad, but some of the things that you're talking about in the document, and I read the \"New York Times\" piece as well --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Do you think, as a Republican, it is fair game maybe not to do it in this way, which is pretty poisonous, frankly, but is there a legitimate way of using Jeremiah Wright's words, his comments, his outrageous still against Barack Obama, despite the fact he's already denounced him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "It's actually unnecessary and we know why.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeremiah Wright", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "But that's not what we have seen so far, have we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "It's never like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kellyanne", "Jeremiah Wright"]}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "So what are you so incensed about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I was laughing because Kellyanne started trickling out the -- you know, the Jeremiah Wright talking points, but then she smartly shifted to the economy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "I feel relieved.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Hilary, you want to jump in there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "I think that that -- you know, this is not the president's choice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Can we agree?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "I think we're going to be certain that by the end of this election season, super PACs have done nothing but bring the tenor and the emotion and the inspiration of this campaign down into the basement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["The Supreme Court"]}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Kelly, do you agree?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "The Supreme Court held 36 years ago that political speech -- political money is speech.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Is it possible to have a great America when you have this kind of vile politicking going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "It's tough.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Anything about the behavioral patterns of these politicians in Washington the last year made you feel less than cynical?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I feel entirely cynical.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Is it unacceptable completely for a Republican like Mitt Romney or his campaign to actually use anything that Jeremiah Wright stood for against the president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Nothing is unacceptable.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Jeremiah Wright"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Has it not always been like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I don't think it has been as much like this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "RBR", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "RBR", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "How damaging is the fact that Barack Obama is now going to do this, deploy super PACs, albeit as scrumptiously as Romney, when he said he wasn't going to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "NN", "NN", "NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "It is one more thing that gives those people who are inclined to withdraw and be cynical and disgusted more reason to do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Romney"]}}]